Guide to the Roy Eaton papers, 1860-2016 and undated. RL.11520
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Roy Eaton papers
1860-2016 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Eaton, Roy, 1930-
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
RL.11520
54.0 Linear Feet
Advertising executive and music director for Young & Rubicam and Benton & Bowles agencies in New York. First African American with hold general creative managerial responsibilities in a major American advertising agency. Noted composer and concert pianist.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Concerts and recitals; Correspondence, General Files; Music scores and lyrics; Printed material; Roy Eaton Music, Inc.; and Audiovisual materials.
Biographical / Historical
Advertising executive and music director for Young & Rubicam and Benton & Bowles agencies in New York. First African American with hold general creative managerial responsibilities in a major American advertising agency. Noted composer and concert pianist.
Born 1930, New York. First concert performance 1937. Attended New York High School of Music and Art; City College of New York; Manhattan School of Music; Yale University; University of Zurich. Concert debut, Carnegie Hall 1946. Winner first competition of Kosciuszko Foundation Chopin Award 1950. Military service, Armed Services Radio Service 1953-1955. Copywriter and composer, Young & Rubicam, 1955-1958; Music Director, Benton & Bowles, 1959-1980. Director, Roy Eaton Music 1980-. Advertising Hall of Fame 2010.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Roy Eaton papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 2017.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles Archives
Douglass L. Alligood papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Carroll Carroll papers
Joy Golden papers.
Collection Overview
Collection includes correspondence, marketing research reports, scripts, musical scores, photographs, musical scores, clippings and other printed materials. Includes audio and video cassettes, tape reels, phonograph records and optical media. Languages present in the collection include German, Russian, Spanish and Vietnamese. Collection also documents the work and collaboration of a number of African American and other minority composers, including Adolphus Hailstork, Chico O'Farrill, Fred Shannon Two Feathers, Scott Joplin and William Grant Still. Companies represented include Benton & Bowles, General Foods, Lorillard, Rhahm Music, Roy Eaton Music and Texaco. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Television advertising -- United States; Radio advertising -- United States; African American composers -- United States; African American musicians -- Correspondence; African Americans in advertising; African Americans in mass media; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Benton & Bowles; General Foods Corporation; P. Lorillard Company
- Concerts and Recitals, 1946-2016 and undated; 1
  - Bernice Eaton tributes, 1992-2002 (Box 1)
  - Concert programs, notes, 1986-2014 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1987-2014 (Box 1)
  - Joyful Joplin, 1992-1997 (Box 1)
  - Keyboard Classics for Kids, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Kosciuszko Foundation, 1992-2014 (Box 1)
  - Meditative Chopin, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Meditative Chopin, 1987 (Box 27)
  - Posters, 1950s-1988; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Posters, 1950s-1988; 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Publicity, 1946-2005; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Publicity, 2006-2016 and undated; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Publicity, 2004-2007 (Box 27)
  - Publicity, 1951-2015; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Publicity--Designs and templates, undated (Box 2)
  - Publicity--Ecuador, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Publicity--Fairfield, Ia., 1991-2004 (Box 30)
  - Publicity--Germany, 1949-1989 (Box 2)
  - Publicity--Germany, 1984-1995 (Box 30)
  - Publicity--Main Street Wire, 1986-2014; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Publicity--Soviet Union (Russia), 1991 (Box 2)
  - Publicity--Vietnam, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Ragtime festivals, 2001-2003 (Box 2)
  - Ragtime festivals, 2000-2001 (Box 30)
  - Rental costs, etc., 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Reviews, 1950-2008 (Box 2)
  - Reviews, 1951 and undated (Box 27)
  - Salisbury (N.C.) Symphony Orchestra--Down Home Blues, 2006 (Box 2)
  - Salisbury (N.C.) Symphony Orchestra--Down Home Blues, 2006 (Box 30)
  - Scott Joplin (Biographical information, Treemonisha opera), 2006-2011 (Box 2)
  - Scott Joplin Ragtime Festival, 1999-2002 (Box 2)
  - Scott Joplin Ragtime Festival, 2000-2002 (Box 30)
  - Soviet Union--Moscow diary, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Western Piedmont (N.C.) Symphony, 2002-2006 (Box 2)
- Correspondence Files, 1959-2012; 2
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1959-1983; 15 folders (Box 3)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1983-1986; 9 folders (Box 4)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1986-1988; 9 folders (Box 5)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1988-1989; 8 folders (Box 6)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1989-1991; 7 folders (Box 7)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1991-1994; 9 folders (Box 8)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1994-1996; 8 folders (Box 9)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 1996-2005; 9 folders (Box 10)
  - Incoming and Outgoing, 2006-2012; 4 folders (Box 11)
- General Files, 1937-2014 and undated; 3
  - Award--Ad.net Board of Directors, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Award--AdColor, 2010 (Box 11)
  - Award--Advertising Hall of Fame, 2010 (Box 11)
  - Award--American Television and Radio Commercials Festival, 1969 (Box 31)
  - Award--Black Employee Network Pioneer, 2014 (Box 11)
  - Award--CEBA (Communications Excellence to Black Audiences), 1992 (Box 11)
  - Award--Clio (certificates), 1983-1985 (Box 31)
  - Award--Clio (physical objects), 1976 and undated (Box 35)
  - Award--High School of Music and Art Alumnus Association (Box 11)
  - Award--Hollis Presbyterian Church 35th Anniversary Membership, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Benny Golson, undated (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Dalmatian, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Infinity Factory: Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Infinity Factory: Writer's Kit, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Jingles schedules, 1955-1956 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Love Will Come Again, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Memos, 1967-1982 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Policies on race, 1963-1968 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Praise file (articles and memos), 1959-1965 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Roy Eaton caricature, 1974 (Box 31)
  - Benton & Bowles--Speech: The Third Column--New Dimensions in Commercial Music, 1961 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Studio takes and times, 1963-1964 (Box 27)
  - Benton & Bowles--Yuban interoffice research report, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Benton & Bowles--Yuban research: Aged Beans commercial, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Biographical information for publicity, 1974-1982 (Box 12)
  - Biographical sketches, 1937-2000 (Box 12)
  - BMI (Broadcast Music Inc.), 1962-1989; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Brian Mackness, undated (Box 12)
  - Composers articles, 1985-1991 (Box 12)
  - Concerts and address books, 1986-2004 (Box 13)
  - Copyright forms, 1958-1959 (Box 12)
  - Day planner, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Day Timers, 1981-1990 (Box 13)
  - Day Timers, 1990-2004 (Box 14)
  - Eaton Life, a proposal for a minority-owned life insurance company, 1994 (Box 15)
  - Garrison Center Partners, 1981-1991 (Box 15)
  - General Assembly Mission Council, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Holiday card from Eaton family, 2012 (Box 15)
  - Index card contact file, undated (Box 16)
  - Index card contact file, undated (Box 17)
  - Joshua Pittman, 2002 (Box 18)
  - Journal, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Karen Phillips interview with Roy Eaton, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Manhattan School of Music exam questions, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Merrill Lynch retirement plan, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 27)
  - Notebook, 1983-1988; 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Notebook--Science of Creative Intelligence, undated (Box 18)
  - Orchestrator template, undated (Box 17)
  - Pension fund, royalties, etc., 2009 (Box 18)
  - Phoenix Films partnership agreement, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Photographs, 1967-2013 and undated; 10 folders (Box 19)
  - Press and publicity, 1960-2002; 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Press and publicity, 1950-1985 (Box 27)
  - Press and publicity--A Little Cigar Music, Please (Stephen Steiner, TV Guide), 1978 (Box 20)
  - Press and publicity--Black Employee Network slideshow of Roy Eaton accomplishments, undated (Box 20)
  - Press and publicity--John Mazurkiewicz (Public relations firm), 1982-1986 (Box 20)
  - Press and publicity--Music Maven article, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Press and publicity--New York Times feature, 1958 (Box 20)
  - Press and publicity--New York Times "In Sugar Hill, A Street Nurtured Black Talent", 2010 (Box 34)
  - Press and publicity--The Advocate "Mad Man on Overcoming Adversity" (Elizabeth Kim), 2014 (Box 34)
  - Rhahm Music--Contract for Tony Bennett, The Good Life, 2010 (Box 20)
  - Rhahm Music--Gwen Conley, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Rhahm Music--Music licenses, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Rhahm Music--Royalties and earnings, 2009 (Box 20)
  - Shiatsu Therapy art for logo design, undated (Box 20)
  - Shot list for "Like It Is" (WABC-TV), 2002 (Box 20)
  - Sketches and caricatures of Roy Eaton, undated (Box 20)
  - Speech--ABCs of Music for Advertising, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Speech--Fine Arts as a Spiritual Force, circa 1970 (Box 20)
  - Speech--Why Music?, undated (Box 20)
  - Speech--Why Should I Use Music?, undated (Box 20)
  - Speech--World Association for Christian Communication, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Speeches and seminars, 1966-1979 (Box 20)
  - World Association for Christian Communication, 1971 (Box 20)
  - World peace/Colin Powell correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box 20)
  - Writing--Elevation of Music, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Writing--Enlightenment Is the Product, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Writing--Meditative Chopin II, undated (Box 20)
- Music Scores and Lyrics, 1860-2014 and undated; 4
  - Jingles, 1955-1960 and undated; 1
    - American Home Foods--Chef Boy-Ar-Dee, Dennison's Chili, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Bird's Eye Fried Chicken, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Classic Malt Liquor "Flying High", undated (Box 28)
    - Country Kwencher (Micki Grant), undated (Box 21)
    - Daisy 2 (home pregnancy test), 1979 (Box 28)
    - Father's Day, 1955 (Box 21)
    - General Electric, 1955 (Box 21)
    - General Foods, 1956 (Box 21)
    - General Foods--Post Cereal "Start Your Day", 1960 (Box 21)
    - General Foods--Yuban "Deep, Dark, Delicious", 1960 (Box 21)
    - Gulf Oil, 1956-1957 (Box 21)
    - Hardee's "Best Eatin' in Town", 1982 (Box 28)
    - Home Products International--Tandy, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Johnson & Johnson, 1956 (Box 21)
    - Keep New York Clean, 1955 (Box 21)
    - Lady Borden Ice Cream, undated (Box 21)
    - Newsweek--Commitment, No. 2, 1983 (Box 28)
    - Newsweek: The World in Your Hands, undated (Box 31)
    - Northern Tissue, 1955 (Box 21)
    - P. Lorillard (Kent cigarettes), 1957 (Box 21)
    - Procter & Gamble, 1956 (Box 21)
    - Remington Shavers, 1956 (Box 21)
    - Swans Down Cake Mix, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Lyrics, 1964-1980 and undated; 2
    - Beware of the Wobbles, undated (Box 21)
    - Jacques Roc miscellaneous lyrics, undated (Box 21)
    - Merrill Silver--Mountain Rush Fever, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Pauline Frechette, Jimmy Curtis--Check It Out, circa 1977 (Box 21)
    - Post Cereals--Linus record album lyrics, 1964 (Box 21)
    - Try Me (Try a Triangle), circa 1977 (Box 21)
    - William Rosten--What's A Nice Guy Like You, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Music Scores, 1860-2014 and undated; 3
    - 1000 Show Tunes Vol. 2, undated; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Eight Variations on Shalom Havayreem, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Five Friends: Suite for Piano, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Ignis Fatuus, circa 1976 (Box 31)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Piano Concerto 2 Piano Reduction, 1992 (Box 31)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Piano Sonata #1 to Natalie Hinderas, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Piano Sonata No. 2, 1989 (Box 31)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Variations on a Guyanese Folksong, 1987 (Box 22)
    - Adolphus Hailstork--Variations on a Guyanese Folksong, 1987 (Box 31)
    - Alan Menken--I Wanna Know; Hangin on, undated (Box 22)
    - Barkman, Michael Masser--Nature's Nectar, undated (Box 22)
    - Bill Curreri--Mr. Physician, undated (Box 28)
    - Charles Harding, Ronald Lockhart--I've Been Looking for You, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Christoph W. von Gluck--Melody from "Orpheus, 1938 (Box 22)
    - Danny Staton, Herb Buchanan--The Writing on the Wall, 1974 (Box 22)
    - E.J. Brisker, A. Heller--Now, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Edward Green--Concertino, undated (Box 27)
    - Fred Shannon--Home to Me, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Fred Shannon, Roy Eaton--Cindy's Laughing Tree, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Fred Shannon, Roy Eaton--Play Pat with Patti, Daddy, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Fred Shannon, Roy Eaton--Thunderbird, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Fred Shannon, Roy Eaton--What Would You Do?, 1970 (Box 22)
    - Frederick Chopin--Scherzo, Deux Nocturnes, undated (Box 22)
    - Ginger Greco, Roy Eaton--Love is God, undated (Box 22)
    - Gwendolyn Merril Maus--The Austin Blues, 1981 (Box 28)
    - Infinity Factory S-1--Shapes--Micki Grant, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-2--When a Wiggle Gets a Wobble; Triangle--Micki Grant, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-3--Don't Mess With a Guess--Jay Bacal, Tommy Goodman, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-3--Don't Mess With a Guess--Jay Bacal, Tommy Goodman, 1977 (Box 31)
    - Infinity Factory S-4A, 4B, 4C--Metric (length, weight, and volume)--Roy Eaton, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-5, 5B--How to Measure; Weighing Song--Pauline Frechette, Jimmy Curtis, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-6--Learn to Estimate--Roy Eaton, 1977 (Box 28)
    - Infinity Factory S-7--Problem Solving--Arranger Chico O'Farill, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-7--Problem Solving--Arranger Chico O'Farill, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-8--Scale Song--Pauline Frechette, Jimmy Curtis--Arranger Chico O'Farrill, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-8--Scale Song--Pauline Frechette, Jimmy Curtis--Arranger Chico O'Farrill, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-9--Scale Drawing and Model Song, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-9--Scale Drawing and Model Song--Suzanne Fazio--Arranger Chico O-Farrill, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-10--Mapping Song--Pauline Frechette, Jimmy Curtis, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-10--Mapping Song--Pauline Frechette, Jimmy Curtis, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-11--Angles--Ginny Redington, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-13--Rate--Horace Diaz, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-13--Rate--Horace Diaz, 1977 (Box 28)
    - Infinity Factory S-14--The Speed Song--Bobby Gosh--Arranger Chico O'Farrill, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-14--The Speed Song--Bobby Gosh--Arranger Chico O'Farrill, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-15--Graph Song--Chico O' Farrill, Oscar Jaimes, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-15--Graph Song--Chico O' Farrill, Oscar Jaimes, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-17--Volume--John Cross, Roy Eaton--Arranger Lou Hemsey, 1977 (Box 28)
    - Infinity Factory S-18--Time--Roy Eaton, Micki Grant, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-19--Temperature Song--Ginny Redington, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-19--Temperature Song--Ginny Redington, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-20--Zero Point--Enid Futterman, Ellen de Leston, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-22--Approximate--Enid Futterman, Charlie Smalls, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-23--Percentages, Decimals, and Fractions--Ginny Redington--Arranger Lou Hemsey, 1977 (Box 28)
    - Infinity Factory S-24--You Got it All--Ginny Redington, 1977 (Box 28)
    - Infinity Factory S-25--Averages--David Small, Horace Diaz, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-25--Averages--David Small, Horace Diaz, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-26--Probability--Enid Futterman, Michael Cohen--Arranger Lou Hemsey, 1977 (Box 28)
    - Infinity Factory S-27--Tricks--Jeff Klein, Enid Futterman, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-27--Tricks--Jeff Klein, Enid Futterman, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-28--Place Values, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-29--Negative Numbers--Gary Dodsen, Roy Eaton, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-30--The Decimal--Arranger Chico O'Farrill, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-30--The Decimal--Arranger Chico O'Farrill, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Infinity Factory S-31--Infinity--Fred Lipsius--Arranger Roy Eaton, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-32--Theme #3--Roy Eaton--Crystal Wilkinson, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Infinity Factory S-33--The Beast--Roy Eaton, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Jacques Roc--Now is Time for Love, 1979 (Box 27)
    - Jacques Roc, Roy Eaton--Let the Music Play (I'm a Disco Freak), 1979 (Box 27)
    - Jacques Roc, Roy Eaton--Let the Music Play (I'm a Disco Freak); Ron Frangipane, Roy Eaton--Love Will Come Again, 1979 (Box 32)
    - Jessica Seymour, Roy Eaton--Lost Love, undated (Box 27)
    - Joe Bacal, Roy Eaton--Your Mother, 1977 (Box 28)
    - John Field--Quatrieme Concerto, undated (Box 31)
    - John Philip Sousa--The Washington Post, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Linus record albums, 1964
    - Louis Moreau Gottschalk--Ojos Criollos, 1860 (Box 22)
    - Louis Moreau Gottschalk--Overture Guillaume Tell, 1864 (Box 22)
    - Marilyn Cooper--Quiet Please, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Marilyn Cooper--Quiet Please, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Marilyn Cooper--Two Brothers, undated (Box 22)
    - Mary Hockaday, Roy Eaton--Live a Little, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Mary Hockaday, Roy Eaton--The Lonely Soldier, 1968 (Box 22)
    - Mary Wallach, Roy Eaton--We're Much Better Than You, undated (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous lyrics and scores, 1979 and undated (Box 29)
    - Musician's Atlas, undated (Box 22)
    - Musician's Atlas, undated (Box 23)
    - Phil Bennet--Who will Care?; You Can Never Tell, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Roy Eaton (arranger)--A Mighty Fortress, 1963 (Box 32)
    - Roy Eaton--Brighter Day (Box 23)
    - Roy Eaton--How Long, undated (Box 23)
    - Roy Eaton--Let Me In, undated (Box 23)
    - Roy Eaton--Majestic Sunset, 2014 (Box 23)
    - Roy Eaton--Metric Song, undated (Box 27)
    - Roy Eaton--Mother May I, undated (Box 27)
    - Roy Eaton--Mother May I, undated; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Roy Eaton--Mother May I, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Roy Eaton--Over a Cup of Coffee, undated (Box 29)
    - Roy Eaton (?)--Quartette R.E., undated (Box 32)
    - Roy Eaton--Up the Avenue, undated (Box 29)
    - Roy Eaton--Up the Avenue, undated (Box 32)
    - Roy Eaton--Where?, 1967 (Box 29)
    - Roy Eaton, Jacques Roc--Love Will Come Again, undated (Box 32)
    - Russ Jolly, Pat Cook, Roy Eaton--This Man Said, 1977 (Box 23)
    - Scott Joplin scores, 1901-1909 (Box 23)
    - Susan Ring--Miscellaneous scores, undated (Box 23)
    - Suzanne Ciani--Dream Songs, 1995 (Box 23)
    - Suzanne Ciani--New Age Piano, 1991 (Box 23)
    - Suzanne Fazio--Without the Pain of You, 1979 (Box 27)
    - The Shape of Things, undated (Box 23)
    - Tito Francia--Sonata, undated (Box 23)
    - Tom Juerden--The Khadine (used in a Yardley commercial), undated (Box 29)
    - William Grant Still--Kaintuck, 1935 (Box 32)
- Printed Material, 1977-2014 and undated; 5
  - Acoustiguide brochure, undated (Box 23)
  - AFTRA 1977-1980 National Code of Fair Practice for Phonograph Recordings (Box 23)
  - AFTRA Welfare Fund--Your Benefits, 1980 (Box 23)
  - Anne Bryant--Click Track Mathematical System for Film Scoring, 1996 (Box 23)
  - Ayurvedic Medicine, 1980s-1990s (Box 23)
  - Ayurvedic Medicine--Maharishi Ayur-Vedi, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Ayurvedic Medicine--Maharishi Jyotish, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Bruno Furst--Course in Memory and Concentration, undated (Box 24)
  - City College of New York newsletters, 2000-2014 (Box 24)
  - Clio Awards magazine, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Derek Sivers (CD Baby)/Articles on marketing music, 2006 (Box 24)
  - Diversity Achievement and Mosaic Awards and Forum, 2010 (Box 24)
  - DMB&B AdVenture, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Entrepreneur's Coaching Program, 1988 (Box 24)
  - Eric Butterworth--New Tempo for Living; The Law and the Promise, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Eric Butterworth--The Great Awakening, 2001 (Box 24)
  - Eric Butterworth Speaks--#1 What Am I Here For?, undated (Box 24)
  - George Holiday "Have a Gluey Christmas", undated (Box 27)
  - High School of Music and Art publications, 1990-1997 (Box 24)
  - Keyboard Classics for Kids, undated (Box 24)
  - Main Street Wire, 1986
  - Manhattan School of Music faculty directory, 2006 (Box 24)
  - Manhattan School of Music publications, 1995-2014 (Box 24)
  - Marc Fedricks--Click Tricks for Click Tracks lessons, 1991; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - MIU (Maharishi International University) World, 1991 (Box 32)
  - National Association of Negro Musicians Convention, 1995 (Box 25)
  - Nhac Vien TP. Ho Chi Minh 1975-1995, undated (Box 25)
  - Raymond F. Kravis for the Performing Arts concert schedule 2005-2006 (Box 25)
  - Sherry Winston--Look Inside the Record Industry, undated (Box 25)
  - Unity Center--Centerpeace newsletter, 2001 (Box 25)
- Roy Eaton Music, Inc., 1961-1995 and undated; 6
  - Advertisement designs, undated (Box 25)
  - Advertisement designs, 1982-1986; 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Ariel Joseph, 1993 (Box 25)
  - Billing information, 1986-1988; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - Blank forms, undated (Box 25)
  - Blank forms, undated (Box 27)
  - BTR (Broadcast Traffic and Residuals) service agreement, 1989 (Box 26)
  - Cash disbursements, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
  - Clio entries, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Composer biographies (Anne Bryant, Benny Golson), 1994 (Box 26)
  - Fred Shannon, 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - General, 1982-1984 (Box 26)
  - Glory Foods, 1992-1994 (Box 26)
  - Invoices, 1986-1990; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Lester Lanin album, 1961 (Box 26)
  - Music agreement contracts, undated (Box 26)
  - Musical goals master plan, undated (Box 26)
  - Musician contracts, 1987-1993 (Box 27)
  - Newsweek: The World in Your Hands advertisement design, undated (Box 32)
  - Recording estimates, 1985-1988 (Box 26)
  - Studio reports, 1983-1995; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Weekly cash expense reports, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Yavapai Story (Film) cue sheets, clearances, 1993 (Box 27)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1955-2014 and undated; 7
  - Audio Tape Reels, 1955-1991 and undated; 4
    - Ballantine Ale :60, 1988 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-001)
    - Battle Ball, 1989 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-002)
    - Benton & Bowles--Former Clients, 1963-1965 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-003)
      Scope and Contents
      Beech-Nut; Paxton; Sodaburst; Yuban; Noforms; Parliament; Glass Container Manufacturers; Stars and Stripes; Saratoga
    - Benton & Bowles--Hardee's compilation (52 tracks), 1980 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-004)
    - Benton & Bowles--Hardee's, Hasbro, 1975 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-005)
    - Benton & Bowles--Instant Maxwell House, 1959 (Box AV1, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-006)
    - Benton & Bowles--Infinity Factory (11 tracks), 1977 (Box AV2, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-007)
    - Benton & Bowles--Infinity Factory reel 1, 1977 (Box AV2, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-008)
    - Benton & Bowles--Infinity Factory reel 2, 1977 (Box AV2, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-009)
    - Benton & Bowles--Infinity Factory instrumental tracks, 1977 (Box AV2, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-010)
    - Benton & Bowles--Compilation Ambush to Hasbro, 1973 (Box AV2, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-011)
      Ambush; Pampers; Muscular Dystrophy; Bounce; New Dawn; Horizon; Cool Whip; Nyquil; Charmin; Nytol; Weebles; Hasbro
    - Benton & Bowles--Zest, 1955-1967 (Box AV3, Audio-reel RL11520-RR-012)